TAP version 13
# Subtest: selecting an audio-only playlist entry keeps its actual index
ok 1 - selecting an audio-only playlist entry keeps its actual index
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3535
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: home restore cannot seek a subsequently selected track
ok 2 - home restore cannot seek a subsequently selected track
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7266
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: home keeps shared time while metadata is pending
ok 3 - home keeps shared time while metadata is pending
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.1605
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: paused 42-second handoff survives pending metadata and resumes persistence after seeking
ok 4 - paused 42-second handoff survives pending metadata and resumes persistence after seeking
  ---
  duration_ms: 2.4457
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: next before metadata cannot apply A's saved seek to B
ok 5 - next before metadata cannot apply A's saved seek to B
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.4616
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: metadata from the old resource cannot complete the new selection's pending handoff
ok 6 - metadata from the old resource cannot complete the new selection's pending handoff
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.8265
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: A to B to A before metadata does not revive A's obsolete restored position
ok 7 - A to B to A before metadata does not revive A's obsolete restored position
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.8634
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: home selection stops at yard; origin never changes on a save
ok 8 - home selection stops at yard; origin never changes on a save
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.2627
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: yard origin and intent survive home saves and blocked autoplay
ok 9 - yard origin and intent survive home saves and blocked autoplay
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6306
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: boundary stop policy survives handoff and completion; explicit selection clears it
ok 10 - boundary stop policy survives handoff and completion; explicit selection clears it
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6583
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: explicit home selection replaces yard origin even for same file
ok 11 - explicit home selection replaces yard origin even for same file
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.3711
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: player is visible and disabled before a track is chosen, with no close control
ok 12 - player is visible and disabled before a track is chosen, with no close control
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0044
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: Escape without a dialog retains playback and the persistent panel
ok 13 - Escape without a dialog retains playback and the persistent panel
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0567
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: player controls never trigger the global track picker
ok 14 - player controls never trigger the global track picker
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7456
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: a pixel-quantized wheel stops its RAF instead of running forever near the target
ok 15 - a pixel-quantized wheel stops its RAF instead of running forever near the target
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.5583
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: spatial listening surface retains identity and approved copy
ok 16 - spatial listening surface retains identity and approved copy
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.6008
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: spatial control system has large targets and responsive low-height mode
ok 17 - spatial control system has large targets and responsive low-height mode
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.2005
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: mobile uses an actual baked logo asset and no decorative scene loop
ok 18 - mobile uses an actual baked logo asset and no decorative scene loop
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.0252
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: listening room keeps original copy and infinite two-way scrolling
ok 19 - listening room keeps original copy and infinite two-way scrolling
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3372
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: listening room exposes a complete transport
ok 20 - listening room exposes a complete transport
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.2372
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: closed chat has only the accessible compact opener, no teaser
ok 21 - closed chat has only the accessible compact opener, no teaser
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.7721
  type: 'test'
  ...
# PASS: street return
# Subtest: tests\\street-return.test.cjs
ok 7 - tests\\street-return.test.cjs
  ---
  duration_ms: 39.3177
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: text links and blank space never select a nearby/underlying song
ok 23 - text links and blank space never select a nearby/underlying song
  ---
  duration_ms: 1.6336
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: touch starts scrolling without selecting; the completed tap still selects
ok 24 - touch starts scrolling without selecting; the completed tap still selects
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.5544
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..24
# tests 24
# suites 0
# pass 24
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 82.3102
